aviationjobsearch.com 2014-02-14

# Privacy Policy | Aviation Job Search

We make every effort to comply with our obligations under the 1998 Data Protection Act. Additionally, we understand the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of your CV and other information stored about you while using the website.

Any visitor to the Website may review the contents and information of all areas except the job seeker area which can only be accessed through a unique email address and password.

The Website also contains links to other websites and the Website takes no responsibility for their content, accuracy, privacy policies and performance of such websites. Any comments or queries in relation to such linked websites should be directed to the relevant contact for such websites.

Registration deems acceptance that we may use your registered name and email address to inform you about other related services and products, either directly or in-directly by disclosing your registered name and email address to relevant third party companies/organisations.

You also agree that the Website may disclose your Personal Data to:

  * A sub-contractor who needs such information in order to enable us to perform the service.
  * Any related company to the Website.
  * A proposed or actual purchaser of part or all of the business.

The Website accepts no responsibility for any transmission of viruses from the Website.

**Job seeker area, profile and CV database**

When you register in the job seeker area we need to know your name, email address and other information about you. Contact and other details you supply as part of the registration process are stored by us and used to provide you with the information you have requested.

You can only access your jobseeker area by entering your unique email address and password. You must not divulge your email address and password to any other third party. The Website will not be responsible for the consequences of a third party accessing your account using your email address and password.

You may store your CV in the job seeker area which gives recruiting companies access to your CV details. If you do not want to make your CV available to recruiters you must explicitly opt out when uploading your CV to the site. Permission to give access to your CV will be implied for any job seeker that does not opt out.

Your CV can only be deleted by you as an individual, unless deleted by the Website.

Please note that AviationJobSearch.com reserves the right to remove from our database, CVs which include any content that we consider to be illegal or offensive.

In submitting the registration form to us, you acknowledge that you have read, understood and accepted the terms of this Privacy Statement.

 **Updating Your Information**

You are solely responsible for the information you provide and for keeping that information updated. You can remove any of the information that the Website stores about you, at any time, by logging on to your account.

If you choose to create a profile and upload a CV to our database, we rely on you to ensure that your details are kept up to date. You should update your CV at least every six months, particularly if your contact details have changed. You will still be able to log in at any time and update your CV and profile.

**Advertiser Area**

Upon registration, recruiters can place advertisements by accessing their recruiter area by using their unique username and password.

**Data Protection Registration**

The Website complies with the Data protection Act 1998. All personal data that is processed by the Website is for the purpose of contacting you about services in which you may be interested.

The personal data may be used by:

  * The Website
  * Any member of the group of companies of which the Website is a member.
  * Agents acting on behalf of the Website or any member of the group of companies of which the Website is a member.

If you require copies of any personal data held about you by the Website, you may make a written request to us for such data. There is a fee for the provision of this service.

We reserve the right to access and disclose any information to comply with applicable laws and lawful requests by any appropriate authorities.

 **  
Security and protecting your Information**

The Website servers are sited in a secure location and access is by authorised personnel only. The Website is protected against unauthorised access using the latest security devices and 'firewalls'. 

 **Statistical Information**

We provide aggregate statistical information about site visitors and users to recruiters (such as the number of CVs on the database, or the number of visitors to the site) and for other lawful purposes. We provide this information to customers, advertisers, suppliers and other reputable third parties. This will not include any information that enables them to identify individuals. The Website will also use the aggregate data to identify employment trends across different industries, such as salary averages.
